<Page>
	<Box
		display="flex"
		flexDirection="column"
		gap="2"
		sx:mb="200px"
		sx:mt="1em"
		sx:width="100%"
		sx:maxWidth="800px"
		sx:mx="auto"
	>
		<Typography variant="h1"> Welcome </Typography>
		<!-- prettier-ignore -->
		<Markdown>
			> NOTE: this is just some chatGPT-generated text
			> this is an example of an issue/job tracker.

			## Introduction

			Welcome to ExampleJobBoard, your all-in-one project management software solution. ExampleJobBoard is designed to streamline your project planning, collaboration, and execution processes. Whether you're a small business owner, a project manager in a large corporation, or a freelance professional, ExampleJobBoard has the tools and features you need to succeed.

			## Key Features

			- **Task Management:** Stay organized with our intuitive task management system. Assign tasks, set deadlines, and track progress effortlessly.

			- **Team Collaboration:** Collaborate seamlessly with your team members. Share files, discuss ideas, and keep everyone in the loop.

			- **Gantt Charts:** Visualize project timelines with our interactive Gantt charts. Identify dependencies and milestones at a glance.

			- **Resource Planning:** Efficiently allocate resources to projects and avoid overloading your team members.

			- **Reporting and Analytics:** Gain insights into your project's performance with detailed reports and analytics.

			- **Integration:** ExampleJobBoard integrates with popular tools like Slack, Dropbox, and Google Workspace for enhanced productivity.

			## Getting Started

			Ready to start managing your projects more efficiently? Here's how to get started with ExampleJobBoard:

			1. [**Sign Up:**](signup.md) Create your ExampleJobBoard account and start a 30-day free trial.
			2. [**Onboarding:**](onboarding.md) Our onboarding guide will walk you through the setup process.
			3. [**Tutorials:**](tutorials.md) Explore our tutorials to learn how to make the most of ExampleJobBoard's features.

			## Pricing

			ExampleJobBoard offers flexible pricing plans to cater to your specific needs. Whether you're a solo entrepreneur or part of a large enterprise, we have a plan that suits you. Check out our [pricing page](pricing.md) for details.

			## Testimonials

			Don't just take our word for it! See what our customers have to say about ExampleJobBoard:
			---
			> "ExampleJobBoard has transformed the way we handle projects. It's user-friendly and has everything we need in one place." - John, CEO of XYZ Inc.
			---
			> "I've tried many project management tools, but ExampleJobBoard stands out. It's intuitive, powerful, and has excellent customer support." - Sarah, Project Manager

			## Contact Us

			Have questions or need assistance? Our support team is here to help. Reach out to us at [support@ExampleJobBoard.com](mailto:support@ExampleJobBoard.com) or visit our [contact page](#/contact).

			Join the thousands of professionals who trust ExampleJobBoard for their project management needs. Start your journey to success today!


			## Site Map 
			- [+Issue](#/addIssue) - add an issue
			- [Issues](#/issues) - view all issues
			- [Board](#/board) - view the job board
			- [Gantt](#/gantt) - view the project Gantt
			- [Wiki](#/wiki) - view Wiki for notes and guides
			- [Files](#/files) - add, remove, and upload files
			- [Settings](#/settings) - view and modify project settings
		</Markdown>
	</Box>
</Page>
